Gus Russo papers, Inclusive: 1932-2006, Bulk: 1953-1998
Baylor University, Baylor Collections of Political Materials
- Beyond Conspiracy: The Hidden Dimensions of the JFK Assassination by Peter Dale Scott, Paul L. Hoch, Russell Stetler, and Josiah Thompson, Photocopies (3 of 3), 1979-1980 (Box 43, Folder 9)
- Warren Commission, Existence of a Foreign Conspiracy, undated (Box 43, Folder 10)
- Warren Commission, Staff trip to Mexico City, April 8-13, 1964 (Box 43, Folder 11)